<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>From E to D</title>
    <link>https://frometod.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on From E to D</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://frometod.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My very first post and how I created this website</title>
      <link>https://frometod.com/post/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frometod.com/post/first-post/</guid>
      <description>I am very excited to be writing my first post of this blog and my very first blog post ever! I created this blog because I noticed that it was hard to keep myself accountable when I learn R by myself. Life happens, distractions are unavoidable and discipline is a scarce resource that takes time to cultivate. So, my motivation of creating this blog is to keep myself accountable and track myself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the author and the goal of this blog</title>
      <link>https://frometod.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frometod.com/about/</guid>
      <description>From Economics to Data
My name is Karen and I am an economist. At university, statistics and econometrics weren&amp;rsquo;t exactly my forte. Things were very theoretical and I couldn&amp;rsquo;t see how I could apply all those complex tools outside the academia. However, all of a sudden people started talking about data science, machine learning and how data science was the sexiest job of the 21st century. So, yeah, I wanted to be sexy too and that&amp;rsquo;s how all started!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dplyr</title>
      <link>https://frometod.com/post/dplyr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frometod.com/post/dplyr/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownSo it’s been about more than two months since my fist blog post. The lockdown during this coronavirus kept me a little bit busy emotionally at the beginning but I’m now already used to this normality and enjoying the current state. The lockdown has been great for productivity! I learned how to use the dplyr() package, did the Statistical Inferece course from the Data Science specialization on Coursera and now I’m about to finish Regression Models from Coursera as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>